A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2010-2013
Library of Virginia
- Series IX. Special Projects and Studies, 2010-2013., Extent: 3.5 cu. ft. (10 boxes).
  - Miscellaneous handwritten notes, 2010-2013. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Pittsylvania County - Comprehensive Services Act, 2011. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Therapeutic Foster Care (DSS), 2011. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Therapeutic Foster Care (DSS), 2011. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Health Reform Initiative - Advisory Council, 2010 Sept 21. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Health Reform Initiative - Advisory Council, 2010 Oct 26-27. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Health Reform Initiative - Advisory Council, 2011 May 26. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Health Reform Initiative - Advisory Council, 2011 July 15. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Health Reform Initiative - Advisory Council, 2011 Sept 9. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Health Reform Initiative - Advisory Council, 2012 May 3. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Health Reform Initiative - Advisory Council, 2013 June 12. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Health Reform Initiative - Grants, 2010. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Health Reform Initiative - Health insurance coverage estimates, 2011 July. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Health Reform Initiative - High risk pools, 2010. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Health Reform Initiative - High risk pools, 2010. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Health Reform Initiative - Report (draft), 2010. (Box 24, Folder 8)